<chapter>
  <centertitle>Preface</centertitle>
  <summary> Welcome to (our) course! In this course, you will learn Tamil with more emphasis on modern spoken Tamil. Before you continue any further, go through carefully the instructions to make the best of the product. </summary>

  <subtitle> Where is Tamil spoken? </subtitle>
  <summary> Tamil is recognized as an official language in Sri Lanka, Singapore and in the Indian states of Tamil Nadu and Puducherry (Pondicherry). It is also widely spoken in the surrounding states such as Kerala, Karnataka, Andhra Pradesh, Telangana and other Indian states. Despite official figures, Tamil is also spoken by minorities in several countries around the world. </summary>

  <subtitle> The Dravidian language family </subtitle>
  <summary> The Dravidian language group is an isolate group which differs vastly from the Indo-European sub-branches. Tamil belongs to the Dravidian family. Other popular languages related to Tamil are Telugu, Kannada and Malayalam. Malayalam has more resemblance to Tamil than Kannada and Telugu. These two languages share similarities but not as much as Malayalam. The main difference between Tamil and other popular south Indian languages is that Tamil still uses the same set of Alphabets despite external influences, thus retaining most of the old sounds. However, being one of the oldest languages in the world, it has undergone several changes as for the vocabulary due to invasions, colonization and other factors. Thus, today there are several English words used in day to day conversation and new sounds are represented as "special" characters. The standard version of the language is often used to write and also used in several formal occasions including T.V and Radio. Though In T.V and Radio, both versions are used.  </summary>

  <subtitle> When to use which? </subtitle>
  <summary> As the main goal of this course is to provide non-native Tamil speakers to converse daily with natives and also to read Tamil without flaw, we have put more emphasis on the colloquial dialect. Tamil speakers can understand each other unless and until they encounter a word that is used “especially” in that region. However Srilankan Tamil is not that different from standard Tamil. Thus we have included both the standard version and the colloquial version. It won't be complicted, hopefully! </summary>
  <rec>play</rec>

  <subtitle> Which version will I learn in this course? </subtitle>
  <summary>
•  The standard version, as well as the colloquial version will be in the course.
•  It's up to you to decide.
•  If you want to simply get around in Tamil Nadu and Pondicherry, it's enough to master the colloquial version (though the script is recommended),
•  If you are in Tamil Nadu and you need to watch a news channel, we recommend both the versions,
•  If you are in Sri Lanka, Standard version will be sufficient!
•  As we have made this course as user-friendly as possible, we hope you will enjoy this course. Thank you!
  </summary>
</chapter>
